Guide to the Russell Van Nest Black papers, 1919-1968.
Black, Russell Van Nest papers
- Series I. Correspondence
  - 1955-1957
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 89)
      Murris Efron; F. A. Pitkin.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Allentown Redevelopment, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 91)
      Morris Efron.
    - American Institute of Planners, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 92)
      Gordon Whitnall.
    - American Institute of Planners, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Applications, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - B-file, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - B-file, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 99)
      Park Planning - Bucks County, Pennsylvania.
    - B-file, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 101)
      G. A. Hurd; Michael Rapuano.
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - C-file, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 104)
      Durand, Michigan; Cincinnati, Ohio. Zoning.
    - C-file, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 105)
      Chatham, New Jersey. Zoning. John Reps.
    - C-file, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Central Berks Planning Commission, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 107)
      Central Berks Planning Commission.
    - Central Berks, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 108)
      Regional Planning.. Harold Tokmakian.
    - D-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Doylestown, Pennsylvania.
    - D-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Menville, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - D-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Delaware, New Jersey.
    - E-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - E-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Edgewater, New Jersey, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Borough Planning
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Borough Planning. Planning Division Bureau of Community Planning; Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.
    - F-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Plainsboro, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - F-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      Woodridge, New York; Fallsburgh, New York. Zoning. Seymour Krieger. State of New York Department of Commerce.
    - F-file, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      Highway Planning - Princeton, New Jersey.
    - G-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Gloucester City, New Jersey.
    - G-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - G-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Eric Grubb.
    - H-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - H-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - H-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      Hatboro, Pennsylvania. Typescript.
    - Hamilton Township, New Jersey, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      Zoning. Hamilton Township Planning Board.
    - Hamilton Township, New Jersey, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - I-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      Ithaca, New York. Greater Ithaca Regional Planning Board.
    - K-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - K-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - L-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      Lower Allentown, Pennsylvania; Lawrence, New Jersey. Zoning. Lawrence Township Planning Board.
    - L-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      Lower Makefield, Pennsylvania; Logan, New Jersey. Zoning. Re: "Clary v. Eatontown"
    - L-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Lawrence Township, New Jersey, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      Lawrence Township Planning Board.
    - Lower Makefield Township, Pennsylvania, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      Zoning. Lower Makefield Township Planning Commission.
    - M-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      Mount Holly, New Jersey; Monessen, Pennsylvania; Middletown, New Jersey; Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Zoning. Planning Education. Planning Board of Middletown Township; Township of Moorestown.
    - M-file, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      Montecello, New York; Moorestown, New Jersey; Laurel, New Jersey. Zoning. State of New York Department of Commerce.
    - M-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      Mount Vernon, Ohio. Zoning.
    - Monticello, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      Monticello, New York. Village of Monticello, State of New York.
    - Monticello, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      Monticello, New York.
    - Moorestown, New Jersey., 1955 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Moorestown, New Jersey., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      Zoning and Planning.
    - Moorestown, New Jersey., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Mount Olive Zoning Case, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      Mount Olive, New Jersey. Zoning. Frank Valgenti.
    - N-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      New Hope, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - N-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      Regional Planning - Delaware Valley. Rufus Nims. Department of Navy - Bureau of Yarks and Docks.
    - N-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      Zoning. Rufus Nims.
    - New Jersey State, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - New Jersey State, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania; Trenton, New Jersey. Urban Renewal. Legislation in New Jersey.
    - New Jersey, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      State Planning - New Jersey. Bureau of Planning - State of New Jersey.
    - O-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Ontelaunee Township, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      Ontelauness, Pennsylvania. Harold Tokmakian.
    - P-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - P-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - P-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 48)
      Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Pennsylvania State, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 50)
      State Planning - Pennsylvania. Department of Commerce.
    - Pennsylvania State, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - R-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 52)
      Lawrence, Pennsylvania.
    - R-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 53)
      Bethlehem, Pennsylvania; Reading Massachusetts.
    - R-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - S-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 55)
      Regional Planning - San Francisco, California; Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania; Somerset, New Jersey; New Hope, Pennsylvania; Ocean County, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - S-file, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 56)
      Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - S-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 57)
      Schuyler, New York; Schuylkill, Pennsylvania; Sullivan, New York.
    - Schuylkill Haven, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Solebury Township, Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 59)
      Zoning Commission.
    - Somerset County Park Commission, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 60)
      Park Planning - Somerset, New Jersey.
    - T-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - T-file, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 62)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Armand Tibbitts.
    - Trenton, New Jersey, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Trenton, New Jersey, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Trenton, New Jersey, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - U-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 66)
      Ulysses, New York.
    - Upholsterers' Union, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 67)
      Palm Springs, Florida. Upholsterers' International Union of North America.
    - Upholsterers' Union, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 68)
      Town Planning - Salhaven.
    - V-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - W-file, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 70)
      Wheeling, West Virginia; Winston-Salem, North Carolina. Zoning. Community Improvement Committee.
    - W-file, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 71)
      Media, Pennsylvania. Highway Development.
  - 1957-1963
    - A-file, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 72)
      Planning Society. APLA. John Archer. American Planning and Civic Association.
    - Aero Service, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 73)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. Aero Service Corporation.
    - American Institute of Planners (AIP), 1959 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - American Institute of Planners (AIP), 1960 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 46 a-d)
      4 Folders
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 77)
      Allentown Council of Churches.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 78)
      Planning Commission.
    - Allentown City Planning Commission, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Allentown Redevelopment, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Allentown Redevelopment, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 81)
      Housing
    - Allentown Redevelopment, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 82)
      Redevelopment Authority of the City of Allentown.
    - 50 Year Anniversary Commemorative Booklet, American Institute of Planners, 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 83)
      Planning Societies. Tracy Augur; Charles Eliot; Paul Opperman; Harland Bartholomew; Flavel Shurtleff; Earle Draper.
    - Applications, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Applications, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - B-file, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - B-file, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - B-file, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 88)
      Buckingham, Pennsylvania; Bristol, Pennsylvania.
    - Berks County, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 89)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania. Berks County Planning Commission
    - Bucks County Farm, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - C-file, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 91)
      Collingswood, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Gilmore Clarke.
    - C-file, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 92)
      Arthurdale, New York. Housing.
    - C-file, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 93)
      Metropolitan Planning - Cape May, New Jersey; Cornell. Planning Education
    - Central Berks, Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Central Berks, Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    - Central Berks, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 96)
      Berks, Pennsylvania; Reading Pennsylvania.
    - Christmas Trees, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Clinton Township, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Zoning. State of New Jersey.
    - D-P files, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2 a-j)
      10 Folders
    - E-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Emmaus, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Planning Technician Bureau of Community Development.
    - E-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Regional Planning - Easton. Easton Area Regional Planning Commission.
    - El, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Ellenville. Ellenville Planning Commission.
    - F-L, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - F-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      William Flemer, Jr.
    - G-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - G-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - H-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Hafield, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - H-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - I-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - J-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      Planning Society. American Planning and Civic Association.
    - K-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Court Decisions. F. A. Pitkin.
    - L-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Lancaster Planning Commission.
    - Lancaster Township, Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Lancaster Township, Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Zoning. Board of Supervisors, Lancaster.
    - M-file, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - M-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - M-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      Madison Planning Board.
    - Monticello, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      Monticello, New York. Zoning and Planning.
    - N-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      Highway Planning - Nutley, New Jersey; New Hope, Pennsylvania; New Mexico. Zoning.
    - N-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      New York.
    - N-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - New Jersey State, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      Hackensack, New Jersey. Land Development.
    - New Jersey, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - O-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Office Insurance, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Office Insurance, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 29 a-b)
      2 Folders
    - Ontelaunee Township, Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Ontelaunee Township, Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Ontelaunee Township, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      Zoning. Ontelaunee Township Board.
    - P-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      Highway Planning - New Hope, Pennsylvania.
    - P-file, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      Paterson, New Jersey. Housing. Paterson Housing Authority.
    - P-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania State, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Pennsylvania State, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Q-R, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Q, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      Quakertown, Pennsylvania. Quakertown Planning Commission.
    - R-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - R-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      Regional Plan Association. Planning Society.
    - R-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - S-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      Park Planning - Somerseet
    - S-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      Raritan, New Jersey; Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - S-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 46)
      Schuylkill Haven, Pennsylvania; Sandusky, Ohio. Zoning. Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.
    - Salisbury Township, Pennsylvania, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 47)
      Herbert Johnson; James Kellar.
    - Salisbury Township, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Schuylkill Haven, Pennsylvania., 1958 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Schuylkill Haven, Pennsylvania., 1959 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Somerset County, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - South Whitehall Township, Pennsylvania, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - South Whitehall Township, Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 53)
      Zoning and Planning. Robert Ritter.
    - T-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - T-Z, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - T-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - U-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - V-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 58)
      Park Planning - Union County, New Jersey. Gilmore Clark. Union County Park Commission.
    - V-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 59)
      Routine Personal
    - W-file, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 60)
      West Amwell, New Jersey. Zoning. Map.
    - W-file, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - W-file, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 62)
      Wyomissing, Pennsylvania. Land Development.
  - 1961-1968
    - A-file, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - A-W, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 64-84)
    - A-Z, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 85-104)
    - A-T, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 105-122)
    - A-file, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - ACPI, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 124)
      AIP. American Institute of Planners.
    - AIP, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 125)
      Planning Profession. Ralph A. Garenheimer.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 128)
      Earle Draper.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 129-132)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 133)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 134-136)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 137)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 138)
    - Applications B, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 139-140)
    - ASLA, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 141)
      Application.
    - ASPO, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 142)
      Regional Planning - Land Use Controls.
    - ASPO, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 143)
    - B-C, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 144-145)
    - B-file, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 146)
      University of Pennsylvania. Planning Education.
    - B-file, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 147)
      AIP Commemorative Booklet. Harland Bartholomew.
    - B-file, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 148)
      Park Planning - Bucks County, Pennsylvania. Walter Blucher; Harland Bartholomew.
    - Berks County, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 149)
      Berks, Pennsylvania. Berks County Planning Commission.
    - C-file, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 150)
    - C-file, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 151)
      Fred Clark.
    - C-file, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 152)
      ABM.
    - C-file, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 153)
    - Christmas Trees, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 154)
    - Clinton Township, New Jersey., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 155)
      Zoning. Clinton Township Planning Board.
    - Clinton Township, New Jersey., 1962 (Box 20, Folder 156)
    - D-K-file, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 157-160)
    - D-N-file, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 1-7)
    - D-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Harold Dodds.
    - D-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Highway Planning - River Road, Pennsylvania. Re: Harold Dodds.
    - D-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Regional Planning - Trenton, New Jersey; Delaware Valley. Housing; Apartments. Harold Dodds
    - E-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - E-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      Whitehall, Pennsylvania; Allentown, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Efron Black.
    - F-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      Paris, France; Routine Personal Correspondence.
    - F-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      Highway Planning - New Hope, Pennsylvania. Bill Blightly; William Flemer.
    - F-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - G-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. "Amelia"
    - G-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - H-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - H-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      John Howard.
    - H-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - I-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - I-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - I-J-K, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      Planning Code. Pennsylvania.
    - J-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - K-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. George Kenwan.
    - K-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      Density Zoning
    - L-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      Lawrence, New Jersey; Bethlehem, Pennsylvania; Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - L-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Louis May.
    - L-M, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - M-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      Milwaukee, Wisconsin; Middlesex, New Jersey.
    - M-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - M-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - N-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - N-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      Jack Nolen.
    - N-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      Recreational Planning - New Hope, Pennsylvania; Hackensack Meadows, New Jersey. Historical District.
    - N-O-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - New Jersey State, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - New Jersey State, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - O-P, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 39-41)
    - O-P, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 42-43)
    - P-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. "Dorris" Mrs Philip F. Pullen.
    - P-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 45)
      Landscape Planning - Planning Code (Act 247). Parry Mansion.
    - P-Q, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Pennsylvania State-R, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 47-48)
    - Pennsylvania State-Z, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 49-53)
    - Princeton University, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Princeton University, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - R-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 56)
      Landscape Planning - Planning Practice
    - R-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 57)
      Landscape Planning - Solebury, Pennsylvania. Parry Mansion.
    - R-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 58)
      Planning Profession. Restoration; Parry Mansion. John.
    - S-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 59)
      South Whitehall, New Jersey. Robert Ritter.
    - S-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 60)
      South Whitehall, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Hugh Scott.
    - S-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 61)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Solebury Citizens Association.
    - S-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 62)
      Park Planning - Somerville, New Jersey; New Hope, Pennsylvania; South Whitehall, Pennsylvania. Zoning; ABM. Flavel Shurtleff; Hugh Scott. Somerset County Park Commission.
    - Solebury Citizens Association, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 63)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. William Miller.
    - Solebury Citizens Association, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Somerset County, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 65)
      Park Planning - Somerset, New Jersey. Somerset County Park Commission.
    - T-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 66)
      Trenton, New Jersey. Report, Memo, Clipping, etc. Armand Tibbitts.
    - T-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - T-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - T-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - U-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 70)
      Park Planning - Union City, New Jersey. Union County Park Commission.
    - Urban America, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Urban America, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - U-V-W-X-Y-file, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - V-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - V-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - V-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - W-file, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - W-file, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 78)
      Winston-Salem, North Carolina. Zoning.
    - WXYZ-file, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 79)
      Old Salem, North Carolina. Zoning. Planning aid.
- Series II. Client Files
  - Allentown, Pennsylvania
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1944-1946 (Box 21, Folder 80-81)
      Zoning. Reports, Population Statistics, Maps, Clippings.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1944-1951 (Box 21, Folder 82-83)
      Reports Contracts, Notes, Clippings.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1953-1957 (Box 21, Folder 84-85a)
      Ordinance, Correspondence.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1953-1958 (Box 21, Folder 86-87)
      Ordinance, Notes, Minutes, Memo, Drawings, Correspondence, Clippings.
    - Allentown- Land use and general plan, 1958, 1957, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 88-89)
      Correspondence, Report, Memo, Data, Proposals, Diagram.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - Fourth Street Project- Final Planning State II, 1959-1960, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 91-92)
      Urban Redevelopment; Housing. Planning Commission.
    - Allentown 4th Street Project- Surveys and Reports, Minutes, 1960, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 93)
      Urban Renewal.
    - Allentown Redevelopment- Eligibility and Relocation, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 94)
      Urban Redevelopment. Black, Russell and Vatet, John, "Fourth Street Urban Renewal Project," May 1959.
    - Allentown Redevelopment- Federal Aid (Miscellaneous and Duplicate Materials), 1954-1958 (Box 21, Folder 95-96)
      Federal Planning - Financial Aid. Housing and Home Finance Agency; Urban Renewal Administration.
    - Allentown Redevelopment- Local Public Agency Letters and Forms, 1954-1960 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      Federal Planning - Housing and Home Finance Agency; Urban Renewal Administration.
    - Allentown Redevelopment Publicity, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Allentown Urban Renewal Studies Prior to Fourth Street Project, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Clients B - D
    - Bernards Township, New Jersey, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
      Zoning. Ordinances, Clippings Reports
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 1952-1955 (Box 22, Folder 8-10)
      Zoning. Reports, Ordinances, Legislation.
    - Bethlehem - Report- Recommendation, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 11-13)
      Zoning. Interviews. Gilmore Clark; Michael Rapuano.
    - Branchburg Township, New Jersey, 1947-1948 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      Zoning. Reports, Map Clippings.
    - Bridgewater Township, New Jersey, 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      Zoning. Ordinance, Map, reports, clippings.
    - Bucks County - Russell V.N. Black Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Bucks County, Pennsylvania - General., 1951-1955 (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
      Reports, Pamphlets, Clippings.
    - Bucks County, Pennsylvania, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 19-22)
    - Bucks County, Pennsylvania - Parks, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Extra Central Berks Maps, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      Maps.
    - Central Berks, Pennsylvania - Publicity, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      Clippings.
    - Central Berks, Pennsylvania - Refuse Disposal, 1955,1957 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      Sewage Disposal. Ordinance, Contract, Reports.
    - Central Berks (Final Report), 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 27-29)
      Black, Russell and Tokmakian, Harold - "The Central Berks Regional Plan," October, 1958.